[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Lin Zai.
Sister Chen!
Sister Chen.
Lin Zai.
It really is you.
Li Ming, he...
He...
I know.
Save your breath.
Save your strength.
We're taking you home.
Okay.
Let me help.
It's fine, I can manage.
A-Leh, what are you doing?
She has a wound on her waist.
We can't rule out a bite.
No, it's not.
That happened when I was running for my life.
I fell.
Or maybe I got scratched.
I...
I can't remember.
You can't remember?
A-Leh.
She's Sister Chen.
She wouldn't lie to us.
Let's check her temperature.
Better safe than sorry.
Lin Zai.
"The Last Oath"
(Episode 15: Dao Camp)
Help! Is anyone there?
We've got a wounded person!
When did she get hurt?
It's fine, just a scratch.
Don't move, the wound is deep.
Why didn't you say anything?
Come on, let's get you patched up.
Here, have some water.
Here, Grandma.
Sister Chen, Sister Chen.
Li Ming, he...
Looks like Brother Li was craving a drink.
Brother Li.
The liquor you love,
I brought it for you.
Rest in peace.
Oh, Li Ming.
Go in peace.
Chen Jin is fine.
Lin Zai is back too.
We are...
All doing well.
Don't cry, Grandma.
These past couple of days,
I've been thinking.
This camp...
Let's just stay here.
Brother Dao and his people are kind-hearted.
With everyone together,
It's peaceful.
From now on,
The three of us can stay together,
And look out for each other.
Sure, this place...
is pretty nice.
Lin Zai.
What do you think?
Let's talk.
I'm not in the mood right now.
Brother Li is gone.
Sister Chen hasn't recovered yet.
And Grandma needs someone to take care of her.
I can't let anything else happen to them.
I understand all of that.
But that shouldn't stop us from talking.
A-Leh.
My mind is a mess right now.
I have nothing to talk about.
You're here.
Chen Jin just fell asleep.
Thank goodness you and A-Leh brought her back.
Come sit with Grandma for a bit.
I haven't had the chance to ask you.
You and A-Leh...
How did you find this place?
Actually, I was taken by him.
That day we went looking for wild berries...
He forced me out of the camp.
Why would he do that?
Is he a bad guy?
Grandma, he's not a bad guy.
Even though when we first hit the road,
It was because he had a mission.
But along the way,
He saved me,
protected me,
and taught me how to use a bow.
He's been really good to me.
Sometimes I even forget that he kidnapped me.
Then where is he taking you?
Grandma.
I can't tell you that right now.
If you don't want to go with him,
I'll go talk to Brother Dao.
It's not really that.
I just haven't figured out how I should move forward with him.
Then you should stay.
We can live a good life here ourselves.
I do want to stay.
But A-Leh...
Child.
If you haven't made up your mind yet,
take your time to think about it.
But,
no matter what, always remember to put your own feelings first.
Lin Zai.
Have you really thought this through?
To love a human weapon?
Just kill me.
While I still have some humanity left.
Look closely.
I'm a monster who needs to drink blood.
Just to stay sane.
Changhuan.
What's the point of you doing all this?
You don't owe our family anything.
Let me go,
or kill me.
Either is fine.
I'm begging you.
It's not about repaying a debt.
I want to save you.
It's never been for any other reason.
It's simply because it's you.
Who the hell are you?
What do you want?
Mind your own damn business!
What's that supposed to mean?
Damn it.
I want sweet and sour ribs today.
Yao.
What happened to your head?
You only knew I came home a few minutes late, looking like a mess.
Mom gave me all her attention.
I accidentally fell.
But when I saw you come home safely, at that moment,
the beating I took didn't matter anymore.
As long as I could protect you,
it was worth more than anything.
Everything I've done...
has never been about gratitude or responsibility.
Then...
Then what is it for?
You always wanted to beat me before.
But to me,
all I cared about.
was after you beat me,
the way your eyes lit up...
When you came running to show off,
when you faced a tough problem,
the way you'd bite your pen, refusing to give up...
It's always been because of you.
Shen Changhuan, you...
Are you saying...
what I think you're saying?
Yes.
I...
I always thought...
you didn't feel that way.
So I was really frustrated.
Why...
Why was I always the one drawn to you,
while you...
while you never showed any sign of it?
How could I show it?
I was living under your roof.
Your parents were so kind to me.
And yet I had feelings for you...
How could I have the nerve?
But now,
I'm just a monster.
Changhuan.
You're not a monster.
I'm going to turn you back into...
that shining Shen Changhuan.
Where did you go?
I just went to the cafeteria.
I was afraid the food would be gone if I went late.
It's okay, I'm not hungry.
Give it to Grandma Qiu and the others.
Grandma Qiu.
He Yao, what are you doing?